{
    "id": "d1e49320b2f44671a432a479a7e4a42a",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She has done everything – she has …………………… been a soldier.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "even",
                "often",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4de8574a809244628c4a7061edb97abb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although I lived with her for ten years, I could …………………… understand her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb702e5561f44fbea660f09562b24599"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have …………………… finished painting the house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "always",
                "almost",
                "even"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ac9d50aa9d64407b250104dee07b51a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is my teacher, but she is ………………… my friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "also",
                "even",
                "just"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9bc73249af9e467fb30f63dc457a7463"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. he could do a thing like that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Only",
                "Just",
                "Also"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17253f92f9654737aa82a5dadb7a1e78"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… look in the mirror before starting to drive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Ever",
                "Always",
                "Often"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c67132ca55374cbeb68e7ebab6253947"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are ……………………… going for two days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "only",
                "often"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b06736f2ad8401ca912efe9b0ee142f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some of us want a new system …………………, not everybody agrees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "and",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49ab9ccaf85241d48e63fef89a21fed9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I worked until five o’clock. …………………… I went home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Then",
                "Still",
                "After"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e5b5fdd01dd64aeaaa7d6086f2075d6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He always wears a coat, …………………. in summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "even",
                "also",
                "often"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f1f624c9d204c78b6f7efa9fa2916ed"
        }
    ]
}